In a serene park, a chance encounter begins to unfold.
A man and a woman sit on separate benches.
They’re lost in their own worlds, yet something significant stirs just below the surface.
Three months prior, a girl had sat alone on a park bench, eating bread.
Her demeanor reflected unmistakable loneliness, a keen unease that caught the attention of a passerby.
He watched her, considering how out of place she seemed in the midst of the bustling park.
Now, as that familiar figure resettles on the bench, she gazes intently at something in her hand.
Uncertainty flickers in her eyes, balanced by an undercurrent of determination.
Nearby, a young man stands silently, lips parted, struggling to find the right words to express his feelings.
It’s a moment caught between hesitation and resolve, a tension that holds him in place.
Across the park, introspection pulls at another girl, who grapples with her feelings of isolation.
She watches him.
He’s the boy who concerns himself with her loneliness at school, hoping that just his presence might lighten her spirit.
Yet doubt clouds his thoughts about their connection.
In a nearby office, the atmosphere is lively and filled with chatter.
Colleagues tease one another about Kaburagi’s lunch habits, revealing that he has been dining with a girlfriend from another department.
Their mock dismay fills the air, layered with playful banter, and one colleague invites Sano to join for soba, momentarily distracting from the workplace dynamics.
Within the spacious calm of the park, the young man observes the girl again.
Thoughts drift through his mind, reflecting on the pleasant day.
He notices her eating habits — that she often indulges in unhealthy sweet bread, her reluctance to make eye contact.
Yet, he sees it: her hands tremble slightly, betraying a hidden vulnerability that lingers even now, three months later.
He muses about the weight of worry.
Perhaps she doesn’t even care about him.
The irony makes him chuckle softly, but that doesn’t dismiss the slight heaviness in his heart.
The young woman, seated alone with an ice cream cone, is equally lost in thought.
She yearns for connection, a space where she can belong without the specter of isolation.
At that very moment, she gazes down at her treat, pondering how intertwined their lives have become.
In a classroom, excitement buzzes as students huddle together, teasing one another about a secret.
They tease and guess, while one boy sits detached at his desk, pensive, removed from the lively energy around him.
Back in the park, as Akari vibrantly praises her kaboom sausage bread, her friends reflect on the meals they've shared, sparking a spirited discussion about whether it’s appropriate to enjoy the homemade dishes from her mother.
Their laughter dances through the air, a stark contrast to the silent maelstrom of thoughts swirling in the girl’s mind.
Meanwhile, the girl contemplates her feelings as she observes the boy she’s noticed in the park each day.
She grapples with excitement and apprehension, torn between the urge to share this secret with friends and fear of judgment.
Among the park benches, a figure rests beneath the weight of loss, a laid-off worker who stares blankly at the clouds, pondering his career’s end.
A girl notices him, musing on whether to approach him, to extend a lifeline, aware of her own curiosity mingling with empathy.
As a tense moment unfolds, another girl bites her cheek while savoring a snack.
Tears well in her eyes from the pain, prompting the boy beside her to rush to her side, concerned for her well-being.
It’s a small world of emotions, colliding in a chaotic dance of worry and care.
A girl gathers her courage to speak to him, her bench buddy.
Tension thickens — he glances nervously, while she wonders