From the author of Oresama Teacher and Gekkan Shoujo Nozaki-kun comes Tsubaki Izumi's newest work: "A Gentle Time." It's a story of unexpected connections and the everyday moments that weave themselves into life, a tale of a man and a woman whose lives intertwined through a chance encounter.
It all started at lunchtime.
In the park, something about a lone woman eating bread captured the gaze of a man.
He remembered seeing her for the first time about three months ago.
She always looked a little out of place, a little uncomfortable, as if she were wrestling with something barely concealed.
Her jaw clenched, a strained expression etched on her face.
Then, a sudden, sharp "thump" echoed through the air.
A man, immaculate in his white shirt and patterned tie, stares ahead, his expression carefully neutral.
An ominous "I..." appears in a nearby textbox.
She remembers a time when she felt like an outsider, a girl alone, left out.
The loneliness felt familiar.
It had been three long months since she first noticed him.
He still ate lunch alone in the park, day after day.
Was she projecting her own feelings?
Was her concern simply self-importance?
Kaburagi consistently turns down lunch invitations, his coworkers whispering that he must have a girlfriend from another department.
They suspect he’s dedicated the entirety of his time to her, for the past three months.
Does he know her?
Does she know him?
Lost in thought, the man realized she was back.
He let his mind wander, savoring the pleasant day.
The park offered a haven of peace and the simple pleasure of sunshine.
He worried that she might leave if he upset her.
He knew she was here because she wasn’t bothered by his presence.
He saw her now, and her unhealthy eating habits and shaking hands didn’t escape his notice.
Her gaze wouldn’t meet his.
He wondered if something was true.
He didn’t know for sure, letting out a self-deprecating chuckle.
Perhaps she didn’t even care.
The man considers the situation, his eye narrowed beneath a shadowed brow.
The implication of the events hangs heavy.
Meanwhile, a young woman sits alone, cradling something delicate in her hands, lost in thought.
She dreams of a place without solitude, a place where she can belong.
She pondered the secrets hidden in the companion’s mind.
Perhaps the very park was that sought-after location.
Her thoughts concluded with a resigned acknowledgement: she must continue visiting the place.
Back in the classroom, the mundane reality of school life continues.
"Guess what?", one student asks optimistically.
Two girls beam, anticipation on their faces, while another prepares to clean a desk.
The school building, under a cloudy sky, is visible in the background.
A girl raved about a gift of delicious sausage bread, while another confessed her regret after enjoying a bento prepared by someone else's mother.
It seems even food has its own dramas.
One girl dramatically declared her desire for sweet bread while being berated for not caring about nutrition, and lamented the possibility of her mother discovering her forbidden treat, which would lead to confiscation.
One girl hesitates to tell her friends about the man she sees eating lunch alone at the park.
She recalls the date she first observed him, three months ago, and realizes he’s present every single day.
Meanwhile, an unemployed office worker continues to stare at the sky, his future uncertain, three months after losing his job.
A woman nervously eats a chocolate treat.
She struggles to appear happy.
The man, the one she dislikes, watches, and realizes she is having a difficult time.
A woman cries out in pain after mistakenly biting her cheek, much to the concern of the man staring at her.
The woman takes a deep breath